<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fasanerie Wiesbaden</string>
    <string name="permission_needed">Unfortunately, you cannot use this app without sharing your location.</string>

    <string name="title_map">Map</string>
    <string name="title_level">Level</string>
    <string name="title_info">Feeding times</string>
    <string name="title_code">Code</string>

    <string name="title_name_bat">Frieda</string>
    <string name="title_name_bear">Bruno</string>
    <string name="title_name_chicken">Henry</string>
    <string name="title_name_deer">Hugo</string>
    <string name="title_name_fox">Fiona</string>
    <string name="title_name_goat">Björn</string>
    <string name="title_name_goat_child">Becky</string>
    <string name="title_name_lynx">Ludwig</string>
    <string name="title_name_otter">Olli</string>
    <string name="title_name_raccoon">Wilma</string>
    <string name="title_name_squirrel">Elli</string>

    <string name="title_location_bat">Bat cave</string>
    <string name="title_location_bear">Wolf-Bear-Enclosure</string>
    <string name="title_location_chicken">Bird pond</string>
    <string name="title_location_deer">Deer enclosure</string>
    <string name="title_location_fox">Fox-Badger-Tunnel</string>
    <string name="title_location_goat">Goat meadow</string>
    <string name="title_location_lynx">Lynx enclosure</string>
    <string name="title_location_otter">Otter enclosure</string>
    <string name="title_location_raccoon">Raccoon enclosure</string>
    <string name="title_location_squirrel">Entry</string>

    <string name="map_text">From your location, move to the green dot on the map</string>
    <string name="map_own_location">Your location</string>
    <string name="map_station_btn">Open</string>

    <string name="maintopbar_reset_headline">Reset</string>
    <string name="maintopbar_reset_text">Type \"RESET\" into the text field if you really want to permanently delete your saved game.</string>
    <string name="maintopbar_reset_btn">Yes I am sure</string>

    <string name="info_headline">Every day except Friday</string>
    <string name="info_time_early">11:00 am</string>
    <string name="info_time_late">15:00 pm</string>
    <string name="info_animal_bear">bear</string>
    <string name="info_animal_wolf">wolf</string>
    <string name="info_animal_lynx">lynx</string>
    <string name="info_animal_fox">fox</string>
    <string name="info_animal_racoon">racoon</string>
    <string name="info_animal_racoondog">raccoon dog</string>
    <string name="info_animal_wildcat">wild cat</string>
    <string name="info_animal_otter">otter</string>

    <string name="communication_btn">Next</string>

    <string name="intro_greeting_text">Hello, my name is Elli and I am the park ranger. Our park needs money and should be sold! Now only the pot of gold that according to an old legend is hidden somewhere in the park can save us. Can you help us find it?</string>
    <string name="intro_greeting_btn">Yes, I\'m happy to help!</string>
    <string name="intro_explanation_text">Thank you, you seem to be a real animal lover! In order to find the treasure we should ask the animals, they know their way around best and together we can definitely find the treasure. Wait, what\'s that noise…</string>
    <string name="intro_meeting_text">Meeeeh, my name is Becky. Look meh. I’m just practicing my new dance steps meh to become a professional dancer meh!</string>
    <string name="intro_departure_text">Your dance steps look great! Your parents must be worried. Come on, we\'ll take you home.</string>

    <string name="station_goat_greeting_text">Meeeeh, I’m Björn, nice to meet you meh! We are counting all the goats in our meadow right now meh. However, some guests have also snuck underneath meh. Can you help us distinguish the goats from the other animals meh?</string>
    <string name="station_goat_greeting_btn">Help Björn</string>
    <string name="station_goat_game_text">Look carefully at the pictures of the goat breeds on the information board</string>
    <string name="station_goat_game_question">Is that a goat?</string>
    <string name="station_goat_game_error">Unfortunately that was not correct. But just try again!</string>
    <string name="station_goat_bye_text">Thanks for your help meh, now we can count all the goats meh! I hear you’re looking for treasure meh. Unfortunately, we could not find anything on our climbing tours meh. But the foxes next door are good snoopers and may know a little more meh.</string>

    <string name="station_fox_greeting_text">Hello, my name is Fiona, it\'s nice to meet you. We foxes like to expand our burrow and we are diligent working on it at the moment. Do you like to help us digging?</string>
    <string name="station_fox_greeting_btn">Help Fiona</string>
    <string name="station_fox_game_text">Swipe the dirt to dig</string>
    <string name="station_fox_bye_text">Thank you so much! With your help we could build our burrow even faster. During digging we found lots of earthworms but we didn\'t discover gold coins. You should visit the bears, once they discovered a gold coin in their cave.</string>

    <string name="station_bear_greeting_text">Hello, I am Bruno the bear. My stomach is pretty grunting and I lust after some honey. Could you helpt me to shake some drops out of the bee hive?</string>
    <string name="station_bear_greeting_btn">Help Bruno</string>
    <string name="station_bear_game_text">Move the honey jar to catch the honey. Avoid the bees!</string>
    <string name="station_bear_game_btn">Start</string>
    <string name="station_bear_bye_text">It\'s very great that my stomach is full again, thank you! According to a legend the treasure were hide in our cave a long time ago and then moved to another cave. I\'m sorry, but I don\'t know where that cave is located. The lynx are very smart and they maybe have an idea.</string>

    <string name="station_lynx_greeting_text">Hey you, I am Ludwig the lynx. We want to teach our children how to hunt, but during playing they confound the manual. Could you help us to get the pictures in the right order?</string>
    <string name="station_lynx_greeting_btn">Help Ludwig</string>
    <string name="station_lynx_game_text">Put the pictures in the right order by swapping them with a tap</string>
    <string name="station_lynx_game_label">Picture number</string>
    <string name="station_lynx_bye_text">Well done, becaus of your help we can prepare our children for hunting again. Unfortunately I don\'t know where the treasure could be. But I have heard that the deers are very hungry and they could need your help</string>

    <string name="station_deer_greeting_text">Hello my name is Hugo. Me and my friends are very hungry. Can you bring us some food from the automatic feeder?</string>
    <string name="station_deer_greeting_btn">Help Hugo</string>
    <string name="station_deer_game_text">Scan the QR code on the automatic feeder</string>
    <string name="station_deer_game_error">Please try again, this seems to have been the wrong code.</string>
    <string name="station_deer_game_btn">Scan Code</string>
    <string name="station_deer_bye_text">Thank you very much, would you like to give us some of the food? We live in this compound for a long time. If there were a treasure here, we would have still discovered it. Did you already try it at the raccoons?</string>

    <string name="station_raccoon_greeting_text">Hello I am Wilma! After wahsing all the socks got very messy. Can you help me to find the matching pairs?</string>
    <string name="station_raccoon_greeting_btn">Help Wilma</string>
    <string name="station_raccoon_game_text">Connect the same socks together by tapping</string>
    <string name="station_raccoon_bye_text">Thank you for helping me to sort the socks. Becaus of you the pairs found each other and the socks can be fairly cleared away. Once I found a coin by the pool of the chicken. You should visit them.</string>

    <string name="station_chicken_greeting_text">Hello cluck cluck it\'s nice to meet you cluck, I am Henry cluck. Recently my chicken lay lots of eggs cluck and now there is a big mess cluck. We need your help to match the eggs to the right chicken cluuuck.</string>
    <string name="station_chicken_greeting_btn">Help Henry</string>
    <string name="station_chicken_game_text">Hand the egg over to the same colored chicken.</string>
    <string name="station_chicken_bye_text">Cock-A-Doodle-Doo! We are very thankful and my chicken are happy cluck. We aren\'t very good at swimming and for that reason we don\'t know anything about gold in our pool. But the otter were diving here. Good luck by your search. Cock-A-Doodle-Doo!</string>

    <string name="station_otter_greeting_text">Hello may I introduce me, I am Olli. Today my dad has birthday and I like to surprise him with a birthday party. We need some yummy fishes for the party. Can you help me?</string>
    <string name="station_otter_greeting_btn">Help Olli</string>
    <string name="station_otter_game_text">Tap on the fish to catch them</string>
    <string name="station_otter_bye_text">>Many thanks! Now we have enough fishes for the party. We played a lot of times in the chicken pool and we found 5 gold coins! One time we discovered a secret connection between the pool and the bat cave. Do you think the treasure could be in that cave?</string>

    <string name="station_bat_greeting_text">Click click click. Hello you there, I am Frieda. Welcome to our cave. The mysterious treasure shall be in a cave? Click. Thus far we just heard of it, but we didn\'t see it. Like you see, click, back there is a sealed door and nobody could open it. Click click.</string>
    <string name="station_bat_greeting_btn">Show dor</string>
    <string name="station_bat_game_text">Use TWO fingers to turn the gears to unlock the door</string>
    <string name="station_bat_bye_text">You are a real professional in cracking door locks! Here is a flashlight for you, now you can give the dark cave light!</string>

    <string name="outro_treasure_text">The treasure is actually in the cave!</string>
    <string name="outro_thanks_text">Hooray, the park is saved! Thanks a lot for your help! As a small thank you, we would like to give you something of our find. With this you can choose something great in the zoo shop.</string>
    <string name="outro_thanks_btn">Redeem code</string>
    <string name="outro_code_text">Redeemable in the Fasanerie Wiesbaden shop or kiosk. Simply present it at the checkout and receive a one-off 10% discount.</string>
    <string name="outro_code_error">Technical error, please contact the shop.</string>
</resources>